A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Projects (Grants), RG 3, Subgroup 1 and Subgroup 2 FA005
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (Grants), 1947-1996; 3; 750 Cubic Feet
  - Projects (Grants), 1947-1989; 1
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1970-1972 (Box 525, Folder 3178)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1972-1973 (Box 525, Folder 3179)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1974 January-March (Box 525, Folder 3180)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1974-1976 (Box 525, Folder 3181)
      7 map prints relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1977 March-September (Box 526, Folder 3182)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1977-1978 (Box 526, Folder 3183)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1978 October (Box 526, Folder 3184)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1978-1979 (Box 526, Folder 3185)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1979-1980 (Box 526, Folder 3186)
    - (The) Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Social Change, 1980-1981 (Box 527, Folder 3187)
    - Maru A Pula Foundation, Gaborone, Botswana, 1970-1974 (Box 527, Folder 3188)
    - Maru A Pula Foundation, Gaborone, Botswana, 1974 March-December (Box 527, Folder 3189)
    - Maru A Pula Foundation, Gaborone, Botswana, 1975-1976 (Box 527, Folder 3190)
    - Maru A Pula Foundation, Gaborone, Botswana Tax Information, 1971-1984 (Box 527, Folder 3191)
    - Maru A Pula Foundation, Gaborone, Botswana, 1977-1979 (Box 528, Folder 3192)
    - Maru A Pula Foundation, Gaborone, Botswana, 1979-1986 (Box 528, Folder 3193)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies, 1965-1973 (Box 528, Folder 3194)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies, Tax Information, 1973-1975 (Box 528, Folder 3195)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 528, Folder 3196)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 528, Folder 3197)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 529, Folder 3198)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies, 1977 September-December (Box 529, Folder 3199)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 529, Folder 3200)
    - (The) Maryland, University of - Regents of - Council for Philosophical Studies - Proposal for Funding for Council Programs, 1978-1982 4/5/1978 (Box 529, Folder 3201)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society, 1975-1976 (Box 530, Folder 3202)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society, 1976-1977 (Box 530, Folder 3203)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society, Tax Information, 1976-1981 (Box 530, Folder 3204)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society, 1977-1982 (Box 530, Folder 3205)
    - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of Administration & Finance, Executive Office of State Planning, Office of, 1975-1976 (Box 530, Folder 3206)
    - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of Administration & Finance, Executive Office of State Planning, Office of, 1977-1978 (Box 530, Folder 3207)
    - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of Administration & Finance, Executive Office of State Planning, Office of, 1978 January-March (Box 531, Folder 3208)
    - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of Administration & Finance, Executive Office of State Planning, Office of Tax Information, 1976-1979 (Box 531, Folder 3209)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1949-1967 (Box 531, Folder 3210)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1967-1973 (Box 531, Folder 3211)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1973 June-December (Box 531, Folder 3212)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1974 January-March (Box 531, Folder 3213)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1974-1975 (Box 532, Folder 3214)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1975-1976 (Box 532, Folder 3215)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1976 January-December (Box 532, Folder 3216)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977-1978 (Box 532, Folder 3217)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1978-1981 (Box 532, Folder 3218)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1971 June 18 (Box 533, Folder 3219)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1972 February 7 (Box 533, Folder 3220)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1976 December (Box 533, Folder 3221)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977 May 6 (Box 534, Folder 3222)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977 May 6 (Box 534, Folder 3223)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977 May 17 (Box 534, Folder 3224)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977 August 29 (Box 534, Folder 3225)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977 August 29 (Box 535, Folder 3226)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1979 May 21 (Box 535, Folder 3227)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1979 June 24-30 (Box 535, Folder 3228)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1980 (Box 536, Folder 3229)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1980 July 30 (Box 536, Folder 3230)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1980 December 1 (Box 536, Folder 3231)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1980 December 1 (Box 536, Folder 3232)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Center for International Studies, 1958-1962 (Box 537, Folder 3233)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Center for International Studies, 1962-1974 (Box 537, Folder 3234)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Center for International Studies, 1978-1982 (Box 537, Folder 3235)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Center for International Studies Annual Reports and Publications, 1958-1963 (Box 537, Folder 3236)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Center for International Studies Annual Reports and Publications, 1963-1967 (Box 537, Folder 3237)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1971 June-September (Box 538, Folder 3238)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1971 September-December (Box 538, Folder 3239)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1971-1972 (Box 538, Folder 3240)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1972 August-October (Box 538, Folder 3241)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1972 October-December (Box 538, Folder 3242)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1973 February-March (Box 539, Folder 3243)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1973 March-May (Box 539, Folder 3244)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1973 May-December (Box 539, Folder 3245)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1974 January-May (Box 539, Folder 3246)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1974 May-August (Box 539, Folder 3247)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1974 September-December (Box 540, Folder 3248)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1974-1975 (Box 540, Folder 3249)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1975 January (Box 540, Folder 3250)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1975 January (Box 540, Folder 3251)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1975 February-March (Box 540, Folder 3252)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1975-1976 (Box 541, Folder 3253)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1975 May (Box 541, Folder 3254)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1975 May-June (Box 541, Folder 3255)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - System Dynamics Group, 1972-1976 (Box 541, Folder 3256)
    - Massachusetts, University of, 1965-1974 (Box 541, Folder 3257)
    - Massachusetts, University of, 1974 May-June (Box 542, Folder 3258)
    - Massachusetts, University of, 1974-1975 (Box 542, Folder 3259)
    - Massachusetts, University of, 1976-1981 (Box 542, Folder 3260)
    - Massachusetts, University of, 1982-1983 (Box 542, Folder 3261)
    - Massachusetts, University of, Tax Information, 1972-1983 (Box 542, Folder 3262)
    - MDC, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 543, Folder 3263)
    - MDC, Inc., 11/2/1979 (Box 543, Folder 3264)
    - MDC, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 543, Folder 3265)
    - MDC, Inc., 2/19/1980 (Box 543, Folder 3266)
    - MDC, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 543, Folder 3267)
    - MDC, Inc., 1982 April 28 (Box 543, Folder 3268)
    - MDC, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 544, Folder 3269)
    - MDC, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 544, Folder 3270)
    - MDC, Inc., 1983 September-October (Box 544, Folder 3271)
    - Media Study, Inc., Tax Information, 1974 (Box 544, Folder 3272)
    - Media Study, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 544, Folder 3273)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1945-1952 (Box 544, Folder 3274)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1953-1954 (Box 545, Folder 3275)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1954-1959 (Box 545, Folder 3276)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1959-1961 (Box 545, Folder 3277)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1962-1964 (Box 545, Folder 3278)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1965-1966 (Box 545, Folder 3279)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1967-1969 (Box 546, Folder 3280)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1970-1971 (Box 546, Folder 3281)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1972-1974 (Box 546, Folder 3282)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1974-1976 (Box 546, Folder 3283)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977-1978 (Box 546, Folder 3284)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978 January 31 (Box 547, Folder 3285)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978 January 31 (Box 547, Folder 3286)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978-1979 (Box 547, Folder 3287)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979-1980 (Box 547, Folder 3288)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 April-December (Box 548, Folder 3289)
    - Menninger Foundation, 1944-1954 (Box 548, Folder 3290)
    - Menninger Foundation, 1954-1957 (Box 548, Folder 3291)
    - Menninger Foundation, 1957 August-December (Box 548, Folder 3292)
    - Menninger Foundation, 1957-1958 (Box 548, Folder 3293)
    - Menninger Foundation, 1959-1969 (Box 549, Folder 3294)
    - Menninger Foundation, 1969-1976 (Box 549, Folder 3295)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1975 March-May (Box 549, Folder 3296)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1975-1976 (Box 549, Folder 3297)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1976 March-December (Box 549, Folder 3298)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1977-1978 (Box 550, Folder 3299)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1978-1979 (Box 550, Folder 3300)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1979-1981 (Box 550, Folder 3301)
    - Mental Health Law Project, Tax information, 1975-1976 (Box 550, Folder 3302)
    - Metro North Association, Inc., Tax Information, 1976 (Box 550, Folder 3303)
    - Metro North Association, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 550, Folder 3304)
    - Metro North Association, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 550, Folder 3305)
    - Metropolitan Applied Research Center, Inc., 1967-1975 (Box 550, Folder 3306)
    - Metropolitan Educational Television Association, Inc., 1955-1957 (Box 551, Folder 3307)
    - Metropolitan Educational Television Association, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 551, Folder 3308)
    - Metropolitan Educational Television Association, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 551, Folder 3309)
    - Metropolitan Educational Association, Inc. (Newsletter), 1958-1959 (Box 551, Folder 3310)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1946-1955 (Box 551, Folder 3311)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1956-1961 (Box 551, Folder 3312)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1962-1964 (Box 552, Folder 3313)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1964-1965 (Box 552, Folder 3314)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1966-1969 (Box 552, Folder 3315)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1969-1970 (Box 552, Folder 3316)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970 May-September (Box 552, Folder 3317)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970 September-December (Box 552, Folder 3318)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1971-1972 (Box 553, Folder 3319)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1973-1975 (Box 553, Folder 3320)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1975-1977 (Box 553, Folder 3321)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1977 January-November (Box 553, Folder 3322)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1977-1979 (Box 553, Folder 3323)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1979 August-September (Box 554, Folder 3324)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1980-1982 (Box 554, Folder 3325)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art - Council on Museum Education, 1972-1973 (Box 554, Folder 3326)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art - Council on Museum Education - Background Information, 1969-1972 (Box 554, Folder 3327)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art - Council on Museum Education - Background Information, 1972 March-June (Box 554, Folder 3328)
    - (The) Metropolitan Museum of Art - Council on Museum Education - Background Information, 1972-1973 (Box 554, Folder 3329)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1947-1959 (Box 555, Folder 3330)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1960-1965 (Box 555, Folder 3331)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 555, Folder 3332)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 555, Folder 3333)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1970-1974 (Box 555, Folder 3334)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 556, Folder 3335)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1976 April-December (Box 556, Folder 3336)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 556, Folder 3337)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association. Inc., 1978-1984 (Box 556, Folder 3338)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1969 February-July (Box 556, Folder 3339)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1970 February-May (Box 557, Folder 3340)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1970-1972 (Box 557, Folder 3341)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1973 (Box 557, Folder 3342)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 557, Folder 3343)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1975 April-November (Box 557, Folder 3344)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 558, Folder 3345)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 558, Folder 3346)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 558, Folder 3347)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1980 October 6 (Box 558, Folder 3348)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 558, Folder 3349)
    - Mexican-American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1981 July-December (Box 559, Folder 3350)
    - Michigan, University of - Conference of Asian Environments, 1970-1971 (Box 559, Folder 3351)
    - Michigan, University of - Conference of Asian Environments, 1971 March 18 (Box 559, Folder 3352)
    - Michigan, University of - Conference of Asian Environments, 1971-1972 (Box 559, Folder 3353)
    - Michigan, University of - Natural Resources, School of - Eastern Caribbean Wildlife Program-Dominica, 1975-1976 (Box 559, Folder 3354)
    - Michigan, University of - Natural Resources, School of - Eastern Caribbean Wildlife Program-Dominica, 7/20/1976 (Box 560, Folder 3355)
    - Michigan, University of - Natural Resources, School of - Eastern Caribbean Wildlife Program-Dominica, 1976 July-December (Box 560, Folder 3356)
    - Michigan, University of - Natural Resources, School of - Park Planning Handbook, 1974-1976 (Box 560, Folder 3357)
    - Michigan, University of - Natural Resources, School of - Park Planning Handbook, 1976 April-December (Box 561, Folder 3358)
    - Michigan, University of - Natural Resources, School of - Park Planning Handbook, Vol. 1, 1979 February 13 (Box 561, Folder 3359)
    - Michigan, University of - Natural Resources, School of - Park Planning Handbook, Vol. 2, 1979 February 13 (Box 561, Folder 3360)
    - Michigan, University of - Ninth International Seminar - on the Administration of International Parks & - Equivalent Reserves, Tax Information, 1974 (Box 561, Folder 3361)
    - Michigan, University of - Ninth International Seminar - on the Administration of International Parks & - Equivalent Reserves, 1974-1976 (Box 561, Folder 3362)
    - Michigan, University of - Public Health, School of, 1959-1960 (Box 561, Folder 3363)
    - (The) Mimbres Foundation, 1976 May-August (Box 562, Folder 3364)
    - (The) Mimbres Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 562, Folder 3365)
    - (The) Mimbres Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 562, Folder 3366)
    - (The) Mimbres Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 562, Folder 3367)
    - (The) Mimbres Foundation, 1979-1982 (Box 562, Folder 3368)
    - (The) Mimbres Foundation, Tax Information, 1976-1980 (Box 562, Folder 3369)
    - Minnesota Foundation, University of, 1977-1979 (Box 563, Folder 3370)
    - Minnesota Foundation, University of, 1979-1982 (Box 563, Folder 3371)
    - Misseduc Foundation, Inc., Tax Information, 1967-1972 (Box 563, Folder 3372)
    - Misseduc Foundation, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 563, Folder 3373)
    - Misseduc Foundation, Inc., 1971-1977 (Box 563, Folder 3374)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations, 1970-1975 (Box 563, Folder 3375)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 564, Folder 3376)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 564, Folder 3377)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 564, Folder 3378)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations, 1978 March-December (Box 564, Folder 3379)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations Tax Information, 1975-1982 (Box 564, Folder 3380)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations, 1979-1983 (Box 564, Folder 3381)
    - (The) Mississippi Council on Human Relations, 1983 September (Box 565, Folder 3382)
    - Mississippi, University of - Law, School of, 1965-1968 (Box 565, Folder 3383)
    - Missouri, University of, International Communications - Program of the School of Journalism, 1958 May-September (Box 565, Folder 3384)
    - Missouri, University of, International Communications - Program of the School of Journalism, 1958-1961 (Box 565, Folder 3385)
    - Mobility, Inc., 1952-1960 (Box 565, Folder 3386)
    - (The) Modern Language Association of America, 1956-1958 (Box 565, Folder 3387)
    - (The) Modern Language Association of America, 1958-1969 (Box 565, Folder 3388)
    - Modern Organization for Dance Evolvement, Inc. Tax Information, 1970-1971 (Box 566, Folder 3389)
    - Modern Organization for Dance Evolvement, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 566, Folder 3390)
    - Morehouse College, 1945-1963 (Box 566, Folder 3391)
    - Morehouse College, 1963-1968 (Box 566, Folder 3392)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc., 1949-1957 (Box 566, Folder 3393)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc., 2/15/1956 (Box 566, Folder 3393A)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc., 1957-1969 (Box 567, Folder 3394)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc. Tax Information, 1970-1972 (Box 567, Folder 3395)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 567, Folder 3396)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc. Operation Crossroads Africa, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 567, Folder 3397)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc. Operation Crossroads Africa, Inc., 1961 March-May (Box 567, Folder 3398)
    - Morningside Community Center, Inc. Operation Crossroads Africa, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 567, Folder 3399)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1950-1956 (Box 568, Folder 3400)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1956 February-May (Box 568, Folder 3401)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1956-1959 (Box 568, Folder 3402)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 568, Folder 3403)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 568, Folder 3404)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 569, Folder 3405)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 569, Folder 3406)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1963 April-December (Box 569, Folder 3407)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1963 December (Box 569, Folder 3408)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 569, Folder 3409)
      1 photograph relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 569, Folder 3410)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1970-1976 (Box 570, Folder 3411)
    - Morningside Heights, Inc. - Morningside-Manhattanville Study, 1957 April 29 (Box 570, Folder 3412)
    - (The) Morris Heights Neighborhood Improvement Association, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 570, Folder 3413)
    - (The) Morris Heights Neighborhood Improvement Association, Inc. Tax Information, 1976 (Box 570, Folder 3414)
    - (The) Mount Desert Island Family Counseling Service Tax information, 1972-1973 (Box 570, Folder 3415)
    - (The) Mount Desert Island Family Counseling Service, 1972-1976 (Box 570, Folder 3416)
    - Mount Desert Island Highway Safety Council Tax Information, 1972-1975 (Box 570, Folder 3417)
    - Mount Desert Island Highway Safety Council, 1972-1976 (Box 570, Folder 3418)
    - Mount Desert Island Hospital Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 570, Folder 3419)
    - Mount Desert Island Hospital, 1972-1974 (Box 570, Folder 3420)
    - Mount Desert Larger Parish, 1941-1960 (Box 571, Folder 3421)
    - Mount Desert Larger Parish Tax Information, 1973 (Box 571, Folder 3422)
    - Mount Desert Larger Parish, 1973-1978 (Box 571, Folder 3423)
    - Mount Desert Public Health Nursing Association Tax Information, 1972-1973 (Box 571, Folder 3424)
    - Mount Desert Public Health Nursing Association, 1972-1974 (Box 571, Folder 3425)
    - Multi - Culture Institute, 1968-1973 (Box 571, Folder 3426)
    - Multi - Culture Institute, Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 571, Folder 3427)
    - Multi - Culture Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 571, Folder 3428)
    - Multi - Culture Institute, 1974-1979 (Box 571, Folder 3429)
    - Multi - Culture Institute, 1975 May-August (Box 572, Folder 3430)
    - Municipal Art Society of New York, 1971-1978 (Box 572, Folder 3431)
    - Municipal Art Society of New York, 1978-1980 (Box 572, Folder 3432)
    - Municipal Art Society of New York, 1980-1983 (Box 572, Folder 3433)
    - Museum Foundation of Mexico, 1966 (Box 572, Folder 3434)
    - Museum Of American Folk Art, 1966-1967 (Box 572, Folder 3435)
    - Museum Of American Folk Art, 1968-1975 (Box 572, Folder 3436)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1947-1954 (Box 573, Folder 3437)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1954-1955 (Box 573, Folder 3438)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1955-1956 (Box 573, Folder 3439)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1956 April-August (Box 573, Folder 3440)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1956-1957 (Box 573, Folder 3441)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1956-1959 (Box 574, Folder 3442)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1959-1960 (Box 574, Folder 3443)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1960-1962 (Box 574, Folder 3444)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1962-1963 (Box 574, Folder 3445)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1964-1966 (Box 574, Folder 3446)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1966-1967 (Box 574, Folder 3447)